A Guide to the Papers of Thomas R. McNamara 1967-1976
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Series I: Legislative Files
  - Sub Series K: Legislative Correspondence: Environment
    - Water Resources: State Water Control Board Report to Committees of General Assembly (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Water Resources: State Water Control Board "The Toxicity of Chlorinated Waste Effluents fo Fish..." 1974 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Water Resources Management, general 1971 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Water Resources Management Study by Joseph A. Mir, William and Mary 1971 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Water Resources Research Center, Research Program 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Water Resources Research Center, Annual Reports 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Water Resources Research Center, Miscellaneous Materials 1975 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Water Resources Research Center "News" Bulletin 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Portable Water Supply Feasibility Study for Southeastern Virginia Planning District Commission 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sub Series L: Legislative Correspondence: Finances
    - Auditor of Public Accounts--Annual Report 1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts--Report on Comparative Cost of City Government 1971-1972 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Comparative Cost of County Government 1971-1972 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations on the State's Budget Process-Commission on State Government Management 1974 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Recommendations for the Legislative Appropriations Process (The Council of State Governments) 1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Budget Appropriation Bill 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 27, folder 6)
    - Budget--Analysis of Appropriations and Revenues, Biennium 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Budget 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Budget--Position Supplement 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Budget--Supplementary Appropriations Bill 1973 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Budget Bill for Biennium 1974-1976 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Budget Appropriations Bill 1974-1976 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Budget Supplementary Appropriations Bill 1975 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Comptroller report 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Finances: Federal Revenue Sharing 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Reports of General Fund Revenues 1965-1974 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Revenue Resources and Economic Study Commission Report 1974 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Fiscal Prospects and Alternatives, Staff Report to the Revenue Resources and Economic Study Commission 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 1)
    - "Fiscal Prospects and Alternatives: 1976" A Staff Report to the Revenue Resources and Economic Commission 1975 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Taxation, General 1967-1974 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Taxation--Department of Taxation Annual Reports 1971, 1973 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Taxation--Cigarette Tax 1967, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Taxation--Commissioners of the Revenue, Role of, includes Annual Report of the Commissioner of the Revenue 1971-1972 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Taxation Exemptions for Military and Other Retirees 1971-1974 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Taxation--Local Taxes 1971-1975 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Taxation--Privacy of Tax Records 1974 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Taxation, Property Taxes, general 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Taxation Property Taxes, Reforming the Virginia Property Tax Vol.I (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Taxation Property Taxes, Reforming the Virginia Property Tax Vol. II (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Taxation, Property Taxes, Exempt Property 1971-1973 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Taxation Rent Tax, General 1974 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Taxation Rent Tax Norfolk Suit, Joint Appendix 1973 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Taxation Rent Tax, Norfolk Suit, Apellants, Briefs 1973 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Taxation, Rent Tax, Norfolk, Appellee's Briefs, Appelle's Petition for Rehearing 1973 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Taxation Sales Tax, general 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Taxation Sales Tax, Holton Rebate Plan 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Taxation Sales Tax, McNamara Plan, Early Speeches 1967 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Taxation Sales Tax, McNamara Bill, HB601 1968 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Taxation Sales, Correspondence re: McNamara Bills 1967-1972 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Taxation Sales Tax, General References 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Taxation Sales Tax, McNamara Bill, General References 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Taxation Sales Tax,McNamara Bill, Reference, (Norfolk Ordinance) 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Taxation Sales Tax, McNamara Bill, Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Taxation, State Income Tax 1970-1972 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Taxation, Tax Study Commission, Senate Joint, Resolution No. 15 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Treasury Reports 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 31, folder 12)
  - Sub Series M: Legislative: General Administration
    - State Informational Directory 1973 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Appointments by the Governor 1974 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Management Study, Survey and Recommendations 1970 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Management Study Implementation Reports 1973 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, General 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Department of Annual Reports 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Attorney General's Office of the Division of Consumer Counsel 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Attorney General's Office, War Veteran's Claims Report 1973 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Bicentennial Commission 1969, 1973 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Code Commission 1967, 1974 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Housing (General) 1971 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Housing--HB418 (Housing Code) 1972 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Housing--HB418 (Housing Code) 1972 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Housing--Building Regulations 1971-1974 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Housing--Virginia Housing Study Commission Report 1973 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Housing--Slum Housing in Norfolk 1972 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Housing--Rent Control 1975 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Report of Commission on Insurance and Sale of Securities 1974 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Lobbyists, Registered with the Secretary of the Commonwealth 1974,1975 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Local Government, Miscellaneous Reports; Correspondence includes "Report on Planning, Funding and Siting for Public Facilities" by the Committee on Counties, Cities and Towns of the House of Delegates,G.A. Report on the Governor's Ad Hoc Committee to Review the Virginia Area Development Act; Report of the Commission on City-County Relations 1968, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Milk Commission Correspondence; Report of the Commission to Study the Virginia Milk Commission 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Museums 1969, 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Virginia National Guard 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Department of Professional and Occupational Registration 1970-1975 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Department of Professional and Occupational Registration, Misc. Reports includes Annual Reports of the Department; Annual Report of the State Registration Board for Contractors; Report of the Virginia Commission for Professional and Occupational Regulation 1971-1974 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Personnel General 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Personal "Evaluation for the Commonwealth of Virginia Salaries and Fringe Benefits Classification Plan Maintenance" House Document #11 1973 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Resolution for Study of the State Compensation Board 1972 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Personnel, Compensation Board Study Committee (VALC) 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Personnel Circuit Court Clerks' Compensation Study Commission 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Circuit Court Clerk's Compensation Study Commission, Miscellaneous Material 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Personnel State Police, Compensation and Retirement 1973 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Virginia Supplemental Retirement System 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Collective Bargaining for Public Employees--Correspondence; Other Material 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Personnel "Rights of Public Employees" Study Commission Report 1974 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Deputy Sheriffs' Pay 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Planning Districts, General 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Planning Districts "A Cooperative System of Municipal Service Delivery for the Southeastern Virginia Planning District," September 1972 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Public Records (VALC Study) 1974 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Rural Affairs Study Commission Report 1971 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 6)
    - State Board of Elections--Election Rules includes "Virginia Election Laws as amended to March 9, 1973" 1970-1974 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 7)
    - State Corporation Commission 1967-1973 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 8)
    - State Corporation Commission, Annual Report of the Bureau of Banking 1972 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 9)
    - State Corporation Commission--Norfolk Savings and Loan; Correspondence 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 10)
    - State Corporation Commission; Norfolk Savings and loan; Newspaper Clippings, Miscellaneous Material 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 11)
    - State Corporation Commission; Utilities Regulation; VEPCO 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Commission on State Governmental Management, Reports 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 13)
    - State Library Report for Fiscal Year 1972 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 1)
    - State Property (especially Capitol Square) 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Sub Series N: Legislative Correspondence; Health and Welfare
    - Abortion Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Abortion Correspondence 1970 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Abortion Correspondence 1971-1973 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Abortion Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Abortion H.B.495 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Abortion Virginia Society for Human Life, includes correspondence and publications 1968-1975 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Abortion National Right to Life Committee publications 1969-1973 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Abortion Miscellaneous Material 1970 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Adoption, Special Needs Children 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Child Abuse 1970-1975 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Day Care 1973 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Problems of the Deaf 1968-1974 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 4)
    - De-Institutionalization-The SID Project (Service Integration For Deinstitutionalization) includes the SID Report, Volume I, Summary (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Elderly (General) 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Elderly Use of School Buses for Activities 1975 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Elederly Southeastern Virginia Area-wide Model Program (SEVAMP) 1972-1975 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Elderly Virginians,Commission on the needs of Drafts of Commission Report 1974 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Elderly Virginians; Commission on their Needs; Interim report; Final Report 1974 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on their Needs, Highlights of Report 1974 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on their Needs 1973 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Elderly, Commission on their Needs January-June 1974 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of July-December 1974 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of 1975 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Richmond Meetings April 29,30, 1974 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Arlington Meeting May 7, 1974 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, South Boston Meeeting May 14, 1974 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Abingdon Meeting May 20, 1974 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Staunton Meeting May 24, 1974 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Norfolk Meeting May 29, 1974 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Reference "State Plan for Programs on Aging" 1974 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Reference "State Plan for Programs on Aging" 1975 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Elderly Virginians, Commission on the Needs of, Study; General Correspondence 1974 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Family Planning Task Force Report (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Handicapped (General Correspondence) 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Handicapped, Responsibility of Parents 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Health Care, General Correspondence 1967-1974 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Health Care, Miscellaneous State Reports 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Department of Health--Statistical Annual Report 1972 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Medicine--Eastern Virginia Medical School 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Medicine--Euthanasia 1975 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Medicine "Fifth Pathway Legislation" Medical Students from Foreign Medical Schools 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Medicine--Hospitals (General) includes Legislative Program of the Virginia Hospital Association 1972-1975 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Medicine--Hospitals, Immunity from Lawsuits 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Medicine--Incorporation by Doctors 1969-1970 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Medicine--Malpractice 1975 (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Medicine--Nursing Regulations (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Medicine--Payment of Chiropractors by State Health Insurance 1972 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Medicine--Virginia Medical Society Proposals 1972-1975 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Medicine--Virginia Nurses Association 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Mentally Retarded: Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial 1970-1974 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Mentally Retarded, Treatment 1968-1975 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Nursing Homes 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Occupational Safety and Health 1973 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services (General) 1967-1975 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Alcoholism (General) 1971-1975 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Comprehensive Community Alcoholism Plan 1972 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Alcoholism Senate Subcommittee on Rehabilitation and social Services--Material re S.B. 547 1971-1973 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Alcoholism--Senate Rehabilitation and Social Services Committee--Material re S.B. 337 January-June,1974 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Alcoholism--Senate Rehabilitation and Social Services Committee--Material July 1974-May 1975 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Drug Abuse Control(General) 1972-1975 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Joint Sub committee on Alcohol and Drug Abuse 1975 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Drug Abuse Control,Marijuana 1972 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Virginia Drug Abuse Advisory Council, Resource Manual 1973 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Drug Abuse Advisory Council, Resource Manual 1973 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Drug Programs VALC Committee to Study Combining Them January-June,1974 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Drug Programs VALC Committee to Study Combining Them July-October,1974 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Drug Programs VALC Committee to Study Combining Them November-December, 1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--VALC Committee to Study Combining Them January 1975 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Rehabilitation and Social Services--Drug Programs VALC Study--Reference 1971-1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Separation and Divorce (VALC Study) 1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Social Work Services, Manpower and Education (VALC Report) 1972 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Vaccination (Anti-Rabies) HB1047 1972 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Visually Handicapped 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation, Department includes Annual Report 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Welfare--General 1968-1975 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Department of Welfare and Institutions Report 1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Welfare--Bills Affecting the Department of Welfare and Institutions 1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Department of Welfare and Institutions: Report on State Assumption of Welfare Programs 1972 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Welfare--VALC Report on Public Welfare Systems 1974 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Sub Series O: Legislative: Justice
    - Civil Law--Probate Rules 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Civil Law--General 1968-1975 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Civil Law--Report on Revision of Title 8, Code of Virginia (Civil Actions) 1975 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Civil Law--Counsel for Constitutional Officers in Civil Suits 1970 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights--"Judicial Selection in Virginia-The Absence of Black Judges" Report of the Virginia State Advisory Committee to the United States Commission on Civil Rights 1974 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights--Report of the Task Force on the Effect of Ratification of the Equal Rights Amendment on the Law of Virginia 1974 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights--Equal Rights Amendment January 1973-January 1974 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Civil Rights--Equal Rights Amendment February-March 1974 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Civil Rights--Equal Rights Amendment April 1974-May 1975 (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Civil Rights--Equal Rights Amendment, Miscellaneous Material 1973-1975 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Corrections--General 1968-1975 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Corrections, Division of--"Blueprint for Action in Virginia Corrections" 1974 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Corrections, Divisions--Miscellaneous Reports including "Reception and Medical Center," A Feasibility Study for the Virginia Division of Corrections, Maximum Custody Correctional Institution 1969-1974 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Corrections, Department of News Releases 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Corrections, Department of Comprehensive Action Plan, FY 1975-1984 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Corrections--Virginia State Crime Commission Report,(Phase I) 1973 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Corrections--State Crime Commission Report (Phase II) 1974 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Corrections--Virginia State Crime Commission Report,(Phase IV) 1975 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Corrections--Virginia State Crime Commission Report On Capital Needs of the Department of Corrections 1974 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Corrections--Special Grand Jury Report on Problems Within the Virginia Division of Corrections 1974 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Corrections--Proposal by Virginia Propation and Parole Association 1975 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Corrections--Rehabilitation of Prisoners 1973 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Corrections--Work Release Programs 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Courts--General Correspondence 1967-1971 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Courts--Judicial Statistics (Judicial Council of Virginia) 1969-1972 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Courts--Comparative Analysis of American Bar Association Standards for Criminal Justice with Virginia Laws, Rules and Legal Practice (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Courts--Senate Bills 1972 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Courts--Senate Bills, Nos.1-177 (Incomplete) 1972 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Courts--Senate Bills, Nos.202-563 (Incomplete) 1972 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Courts--Material re: Senate Bills 1972 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Courts--House Bills 1972 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Courts--Status of House and Senate Bills March 1972 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Courts--House Bills, Nos. 265, 266, 267 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Courts--House Bill, No. 265 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Courts--House Bill, No. 266 1972 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Courts--House Bill, No. 267 1972 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Courts--Senate Bills 1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Courts--House Bills, No. 1497 1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Courts--House Bill, No. 1512 1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Courts--House Bill No. 1898 1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Courts--Senate Bill No. 521, House Bill No. 73 1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Courts--Miscellaneous Correspondence re: Courts Bills 1973 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Courts--Correspondence re: Courts Bills 1974 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Courts--General 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Courts--Capital Punishment includes "The Capital Laws of Virginia: An Historical Sketch" by Richard A. Rutyna 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Courts, District--Report of the Judicial Council 1972 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Courts, District--Committee on District Courts, Report on Activities 1973 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Courts--Indeterminate Sentencing Proposal-Virginia State Bar Association (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Courts--Judicial Conference of Virginia, May 26 1973 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Courts--Juries (S.B. No.39) (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Courts--Juries, Recommended Changes 1972 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Courts--Local Rules and Procedures (Judicial Council of Virginia Report) 1975 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Courts--Misdemeanor Study Commission Report 1973 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Courts, Juvenile (General) 1968-1972 (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 1)